And today is day twenty-four.
The guy enjoyed my job and called me three hundred and fifty mangoes on Sunday.
My brother.
Let's go now,
bro.
It's not on,
man,
I'm digging in the other supervisor's car.
And today we're going to coordinate a team and girls,
we're going there.
Man,
I wanted to give you a little present.
I got there,
oh well,
1 cocoa show truffle.
I hope you like pix it's CPF I'm playing ha ha ha.
Before 1 Sunday worked than 1/2 fair looking for a job?
Are you calling,
my brother?
And today I'm here again working as a flyer coordinator.
Bro,
we're here,
bro Sunday works a little quieter,
fewer people,
but what matters is quality,
not quantity.
Believe me, bro.
Look,
Letícia is pulling her protector.
Girl,
How are you doing,
huh?
And there
now i'm at the other traffic light here.
I'm going to exchange an idea with the mine there.
Oh,
come here.
You need 1 water,
1 little thing.
Heaven brought pot.
let's go to lunch
86 whether we don't go,
young man,
let me see this here.
City newspaper All The coldest time is spending my Days.
We're going to eat that has 1 hour of lunch and go back to the hunt.
Gonna Find The World In The Morning.
Okay,
my dear.
Too good.
How so famous?
Oh famous,
only in Brazil am I famous drinking the motorcycle.
We feel it on our skin,
right?
So we do the business we wanted them to do with us.
So to heat a pot,
sell a loaf of water.
Seeing if everything's okay,
right?
Say hello to me.
If you need a chance,
send Zap there.
I am sure.
I send you, man.
I loved kiss on the heart.
Tamo together. Saw
Oh cousin?
That's it,
brother,
give you a boost here,
it's getting cold,
right,
then it's worth it,
we're with you there.
I'm not one to spoiler,
but tomorrow I'm going to reveal my resale plan to you.
So.